{
    "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684":
    [
        {
            "id": 5001,
            "name": "Team name 1",
            "owner": "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684",
            "leader": 1,
            "back1": 1,
            "back1Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 1,
                "onchainId": 1,
                "name": "PolterGeist",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g1_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g1_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g1_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g1_right.svg",
                "brs": 569,
                "kinship": 829,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eys": 3,
                "eyc": 11,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 4
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 5
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 1,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 1,
                "resist": 0
            },
            "back2": null,
            "back2Gotchi": null,
            "back3": 2,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 2,
                "onchainId": 2,
                "name": "Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
                "brs": 540,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "level": 3,
                "xp": 100,
                "nrg": -1,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 1,
                "brn": 99,
                "eys": 100,
                "eyc": 101,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 7
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 10,
                "health": 20,
                "accuracy": 30,
                "evade": 40,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 60,
                "armor": 70,
                "crit": 0,
                "resist": 80
            },
            "back4": null,
            "back4Gotchi": null,
            "back5": 4,
            "back5Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 4,
                "onchainId": 4,
                "name": "Casper",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g4_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g4_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g4_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g4_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 6
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 6,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50
            },
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 3,
            "front2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 3,
                "onchainId": 3,
                "name": "TestingLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWord",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g3_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g3_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g3_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g3_right.svg",
                "brs": 0,
                "kinship": 0,
                "level": 0,
                "xp": 0,
                "nrg": 0,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 0,
                "brn": 0,
                "eys": 0,
                "eyc": 0,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 2
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 3
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 4
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 5
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 6
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 7
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 8
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 0,
                "health": 0,
                "accuracy": 0,
                "evade": 0,
                "physical": 0,
                "magic": 0,
                "armor": 0,
                "crit": 0,
                "resist": 0
            },
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 5,
            "front4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 5,
                "onchainId": 5,
                "name": "Orko",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g5_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g5_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g5_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g5_right.svg",
                "brs": 520,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 4,
                "agg": 8,
                "spk": 15,
                "brn": 16,
                "eys": 23,
                "eyc": 42,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 7
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 5
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 5,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 1,
                "resist": 0
            },
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null,
            "sub1": 6,
            "sub1Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 6,
                "onchainId": 6,
                "name": "Sir Humphrey",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
                "brs": 569,
                "kinship": 829,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eys": 3,
                "eyc": 11,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 4
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 5
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 4,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 1,
                "resist": 0
            },
            "sub2": null,
            "sub2Gotchi": null
        },
        {
            "id": 5002,
            "name": "Team name 2 Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
            "owner": "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684",
            "leader": 9,
            "back1": 6,
            "back1Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 6,
                "onchainId": 6,
                "name": "Nearly-Headless Nick",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 3
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 2
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 3,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50
            },
            "back2": 10,
            "back2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 10,
                "onchainId": 10,
                "name": "Hopkirk",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 2
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 2,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50
            },
            "back3": 9,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 9,
                "onchainId": 9,
                "name": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 7
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50
            },
            "back4": 7,
            "back4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 7,
                "onchainId": 7,
                "name": "Moaning Myrtle",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g7_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g7_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g7_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g7_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 7
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 4
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 4,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50
            },
            "back5": 8,
            "back5Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 8,
                "onchainId": 8,
                "name": "Peeves",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g8_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g8_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g8_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g8_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "availableSpecials":
                [
                    {
                        "id": 8
                    }
                ],
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50
            },
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": null,
            "front2Gotchi": null,
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": null,
            "front4Gotchi": null,
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null
        },
        {
            "id": 5003,
            "name": "Team name 3 Empty TestingLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWord",
            "owner": "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684"
        },
        {
            "id": 5004,
            "name": "Test generated ids, duplicates, leader in 3",
            "owner": "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684",
            "leader": 2000004,
            "back1": 2000008,
            "back1Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000008,
                "name": "Bear Market",
                "speed": 10,
                "health": 20,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 70,
                "evade": 40,
                "resist": 80,
                "magic": 60,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 30,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "specialId": 7,
                "onchainId": 189,
                "brs": 540,
                "nrg": -1,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 1,
                "brn": 99,
                "eyc": 101,
                "eys": 100,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "xp": 100
            },
            "back2Gotchi": null,
            "back3": 2000004,
            "back3Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000004,
                "name": "VIDRUT",
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 380,
                "physical": 150,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
                "specialId": 5,
                "onchainId": 201,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "back4Gotchi": null,
            "back5": 2000009,
            "back5Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000009,
                "name": "Hopkirk",
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "specialId": 2,
                "onchainId": 10,
                "brs": 500,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "xp": 5000
            },
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 2000010,
            "front2Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000010,
                "name": "VIDRUT",
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 380,
                "physical": 150,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
                "specialId": 4,
                "onchainId": 201,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 2000006,
            "front4Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000006,
                "name": "Moaning Myrtle",
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g7_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g7_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g7_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g7_right.svg",
                "specialId": 4,
                "onchainId": 7,
                "brs": 500,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "xp": 5000
            },
            "front5Gotchi": null,
            "sub1Gotchi": null,
            "sub2Gotchi": null
        },
        {
            "id": 5005,
            "name": "Test mixture of my and training",
            "owner": "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684",
            "leader": 2000001,
            "back1": 2000003,
            "back1Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000003,
                "name": "Rare Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 149,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 164,
                "physical": 65,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 3,
                "onchainId": 1000018,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "back2": 2000002,
            "back2Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000002,
                "name": "Rare Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 149,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 164,
                "physical": 65,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 2,
                "onchainId": 1000017,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "back3Gotchi": null,
            "back4": 2000005,
            "back4Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000005,
                "name": "Rare Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 163,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 164,
                "physical": 65,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 1,
                "onchainId": 1000086,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "back5": 2000004,
            "back5Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000004,
                "name": "Rare Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 163,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 164,
                "physical": 65,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 4,
                "onchainId": 1000089,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2Gotchi": null,
            "front3": 2000001,
            "front3Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000001,
                "name": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
                "specialId": 7,
                "onchainId": 9,
                "brs": 500,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "xp": 5000
            },
            "front4Gotchi": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null,
            "sub1Gotchi": null,
            "sub2Gotchi": null
        },
        {
            "id": 5006,
            "name": "Test only training",
            "owner": "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684",
            "leader": 2000015,
            "back1Gotchi": null,
            "back2Gotchi": null,
            "back3Gotchi": null,
            "back4Gotchi": null,
            "back5Gotchi": null,
            "front1": 2000011,
            "front1Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000011,
                "name": "Common Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 147,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 55,
                "physical": 22,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 5,
                "onchainId": 1000010,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front2": 2000012,
            "front2Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000012,
                "name": "Rare Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 149,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 164,
                "physical": 65,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 1,
                "onchainId": 1000016,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front3": 2000013,
            "front3Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000013,
                "name": "Mythical Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 151,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 272,
                "physical": 108,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 2,
                "onchainId": 1000027,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front4": 2000014,
            "front4Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000014,
                "name": "Legendary Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 150,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 218,
                "physical": 87,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 4,
                "onchainId": 1000024,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front5": 2000015,
            "front5Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000015,
                "name": "Godlike Training Gotchi",
                "speed": 173,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 5,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 327,
                "physical": 130,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_TRAINING.svg",
                "specialId": 3,
                "onchainId": 1000138,
                "brs": 569,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eyc": 11,
                "eys": 3,
                "kinship": 829,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "sub1Gotchi": null,
            "sub2Gotchi": null
        },
        {
            "id": 5007,
            "name": "Test valid for tournament with generated ids",
            "owner": "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684",
            "leader": 2000007,
            "back1Gotchi": null,
            "back2Gotchi": null,
            "back3Gotchi": null,
            "back4Gotchi": null,
            "back5Gotchi": null,
            "front1": 2000002,
            "front1Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000002,
                "name": "",
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
                "specialId": 6,
                "onchainId": 232,
                "brs": 500,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "xp": 5000
            },
            "front2": 2000005,
            "front2Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000005,
                "name": "Orko",
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 380,
                "physical": 150,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g5_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g5_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g5_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g5_right.svg",
                "specialId": 5,
                "onchainId": 5,
                "brs": 520,
                "nrg": 4,
                "agg": 8,
                "spk": 15,
                "brn": 16,
                "eyc": 42,
                "eys": 23,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front3": 2000007,
            "front3Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000007,
                "name": "Lead",
                "speed": 10,
                "health": 20,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 70,
                "evade": 40,
                "resist": 80,
                "magic": 60,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 30,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "specialId": 7,
                "onchainId": 231,
                "brs": 540,
                "nrg": -1,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 1,
                "brn": 99,
                "eyc": 101,
                "eys": 100,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "xp": 100
            },
            "front4": 2000009,
            "front4Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000009,
                "name": "Defiant",
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 380,
                "physical": 150,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "specialId": 5,
                "onchainId": 199,
                "brs": 520,
                "nrg": 4,
                "agg": 8,
                "spk": 15,
                "brn": 16,
                "eyc": 42,
                "eys": 23,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front5": 2000003,
            "front5Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000003,
                "name": "Sunny",
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
                "specialId": 6,
                "onchainId": 235,
                "brs": 500,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "xp": 5000
            },
            "sub1Gotchi": null,
            "sub2Gotchi": null
        },
        {
            "id": 5008,
            "name": "Test outdated stats: Orko as Troll; Peeves 100 Speed",
            "owner": "0x05EBFf07711A5B6042c27FDaa683a5c6D55b6684",
            "leader": 2000005,
            "back1Gotchi": null,
            "back2Gotchi": null,
            "back3Gotchi": null,
            "back4Gotchi": null,
            "back5Gotchi": null,
            "front1": 2000001,
            "front1Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000001,
                "name": "Orko",
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 380,
                "physical": 150,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g5_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g5_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g5_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g5_right.svg",
                "specialId": 8,
                "onchainId": 5,
                "brs": 520,
                "nrg": 4,
                "agg": 8,
                "spk": 15,
                "brn": 16,
                "eyc": 42,
                "eys": 23,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front2": 2000002,
            "front2Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000002,
                "name": "Peeves",
                "speed": 100,
                "health": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g8_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g8_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g8_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g8_right.svg",
                "specialId": 8,
                "onchainId": 8,
                "brs": 500,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "xp": 5000
            },
            "front3": 2000003,
            "front3Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000003,
                "name": "Defiant",
                "speed": 146,
                "health": 228,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 1,
                "evade": 23,
                "resist": 0,
                "magic": 380,
                "physical": 150,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "specialId": 7,
                "onchainId": 199,
                "brs": 520,
                "nrg": 4,
                "agg": 8,
                "spk": 15,
                "brn": 16,
                "eyc": 42,
                "eys": 23,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "xp": 820
            },
            "front4": 2000004,
            "front4Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000004,
                "name": "Bear Market",
                "speed": 10,
                "health": 20,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 70,
                "evade": 40,
                "resist": 80,
                "magic": 60,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 30,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "specialId": 7,
                "onchainId": 189,
                "brs": 540,
                "nrg": -1,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 1,
                "brn": 99,
                "eyc": 101,
                "eys": 100,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "xp": 100
            },
            "front5": 2000005,
            "front5Gotchi": {
                "id": 2000005,
                "name": "Lead",
                "speed": 10,
                "health": 20,
                "crit": 1,
                "armor": 70,
                "evade": 40,
                "resist": 80,
                "magic": 60,
                "physical": 50,
                "accuracy": 30,
                "svgFront": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "http://localhost:5173/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "specialId": 7,
                "onchainId": 231,
                "brs": 540,
                "nrg": -1,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 1,
                "brn": 99,
                "eyc": 101,
                "eys": 100,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "xp": 100
            },
            "sub1Gotchi": null,
            "sub2Gotchi": null
        }
    ]
}